Caesar Zeppeli was born in Naples,
son of the famous furniture maker, Mario.
(ｼｰｻﾞｰ)《どうせ 女でもつくって
いい気に 暮らしてんだろ！➡
His father was a proper Italian, dedicated to his family.
見つけ出して ぶっ殺してやる！》
〈シーザーは
青春と未来を捨てた｡➡
To Caesar, Mario was the ideal man.
盗み 強盗 ケンカ 放火
やってない犯罪は 殺人だけ｡➡
When Caesar was ten years old, Mario left without a word.
大人の やくざにさえ
恐れられた〉
They were motherless, and their distant relatives stole all they had.
(やくざ)《小僧
貴様 シーザーとかいったな｡➡
名字は 何てんだ？》
《姓なんてねえ！》
Caesar became violent, and grew to hate his father.
《ハハッ てめえ さては
イタリア人じゃあねえな｡➡
イタリア人は 姓を誇りにする》
I bet he's living carefree with some woman!
〈ケンカをするときは➡
まず レンチで相手を
めった打ちにする 容赦のなさ｡➡
I'll find him and kill him!
そして
動けなくなったあとの 一撃！〉
Caesar threw away both his youth and his future.
He committed theft, arson, muggings, assault...
everything short of murder.
〈これが
波紋の片りんであることは➡
シーザーは まだ知らない〉
Even the Mafia feared him.
〈そして
16歳のとき ローマで…〉
Hey kid, you're Caesar, right? What's your last name?
《あっ…》
I don't have one!
《間違いねえ あの野郎…》
Then you aren't Italian. Real Italians are proud of their families.
〈自分は 父親を殺す｡
かすかに そう思った〉
Never holding back, he started fights with his wrench.
〈だが！〉
《な… 何だ？ これは!?》
With his foe stunned, he finished them off with a single blow!
《はっ…➡
ダイヤだ…
ダイヤが 埋まっている》
Though he didn't know it, Caesar was already using the Ripple.
(ﾏﾘｵ)《小僧！
その宝石に 触るんじゃない！》
《貴様！➡
Then, at age sixteen in Rome...
うっ…
な… 何だ？ この壁は!?》
(ﾏﾘｵ)《ぐあ～っ！》
《うっ！》
No mistake, It's him!
《はっ！》
(ﾏﾘｵ)《ち… 近づくな
これは わなだ…➡
Caesar resolved to murder his own father.
ううっ…》
〈シーザーには
さっぱり 分からなかった｡➡
However!
W-What is that?!
50年前
祖父 ウィル･Ａ･ツェペリが➡
石仮面のために
惨死したことも➡
その遺志を 受け継いで➡
A diamond! That's definitely a diamond!
波紋の修行に 生涯を懸けた
父 マリオが➡
Boy, don't touch that stone!
この遺跡を発見し
壁の中の生物を 倒すために➡
You!
世界中を 旅していたことも➡
W-What's the wall doing?
このときの シーザーには
分からないことだった〉
(ﾏﾘｵ)
《わ… 若者よ 頼みがある》
S-Stay back... It's a trap!
《あっ…》
《このことを ヴェネチアにいる➡
リサリサという女性に
話してくれ｡➡
Caesar knew nothing of the truth.
対抗できる者は 彼女しかいない》
He knew nothing of the tragic death of his late grandfather,
Will A. Zeppeli, at the hands of the Stone Mask fifty years ago.
〈壁に 取り込まれているせいか➡
Mario had taken on his legacy by training in the Ripple,
eventually leading him to discover these ruins.
シーザーが 成長したせいか➡
マリオは
自分の息子と 分からなかった〉
《と…》
He searched the globe looking for a way
to defeat the monsters in the wall.
〈シーザーは 理解した｡➡
父は こんな恐ろしいことに➡
息子を 巻き込みたくなかったから
黙って 家を出たのだ〉
But Caesar never knew any of this.
《ああ… あ… ああ…》
Young man... I beg of you...
《ああっ！》
Find a woman in Venice named Lisa Lisa.
《うっ… 父さん！》
♬～
She is the only one capable of stopping them.
Perhaps because Caesar had grown, Mario did not recognize his son.
Fa...
♬(ｵｰﾌﾟﾆﾝｸﾞﾃｰﾏ)
Caesar realized his father had left to keep his children safe from this dreadful affair.
Hurry... hurry, you must go!
♬ 静寂の底から
♬ 目覚めるその柱たち 時を越え
Father!
♬ 深紅の血潮が
♬ 立ち上がる勇気を
♬ 惹きあわせる
Shijima no soko kara
From out of the stillness
♬ 受け継ぐ愛を 宿命と呼ぶなら
Timing:
Fadeout4
♬ 微笑む目で 次の手を
Mezameru sono hashira tachi
The Pillars of the past are awakening
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Toki wo koe
To the dawn of a new day
Editor:
Tonitonichopchop
Shinku no chishio ga
The river of crimson blood within you
♬ 闇を欺いて
刹那を躱して
Fadeout4
Typesetting:
♬ 刃すり抜け奴らの間隙を突け
Mazrim
Quality Check:
Tachiagaru yuuki wo hikiawaseru
Carries with it the courage to stand and fight
♬ つらぬいた信念が 未来を拓く
Uketsugu ai wo sadame to yobu nara
Even if the love I feel is just part of my legacy...
♬ Like a Bloody Storm
熱くLike a Bloody Stone
♬ 血脈に
刻まれた因縁に
Hohoemu me de tsugi no te wo
I'll still be smiling as I stay one step ahead
♬ 浮き上がる消えない誇りの絆
♬ 握りしめて
Yami wo azamuite setsuna wo kawashite
Defying the darkness and dodging death at every turn
Encoding:
Fadeout4
Yaiba surinuke yatsura no suki wo tsuke
Slipping past the knife's edge and striking when you least expect
Tsuranuita omoi ga mirai wo hiraku
The emotions running through me blaze a path to the future...
Raw Hunter: WRRRRY
Like a bloody storm
Atsuku like a bloody storm
Burning like a bloody storm
Ketsumyaku ni kizamareta innen ni
When the time comes to end the vendetta carried by our blood
Ukiagaru kienai hokori no kizuna
Remember that the bonds of pride will carry you through any storm
Nigirishimete
So hold them close
http://www.some-stuffs.com
Episode 20: "Caesar's Lonely Youth"
I see...
(ｼﾞｮｾﾌ)そうだったのか｡
Caesar's misunderstanding led to his hatred...
(ﾘｻﾘｻ)シーザーの誤解からくる
憎しみの深さは➡
...which in turn became pride for his father and family.
そのまま 父への 一族への
誇りの高さとなったのです｡
So Caesar picked up where his father had left off.
そして
シーザーは 父の跡を継ぎ➡
波紋の修行に入りました｡
So it was Cars who killed Caesar's father...
カーズは
シーザーのおやじの敵｡
Forgive me, Caesar.
すまなかったな シーザー｡
I didn't mean to speak ill of your family.
お前の一族への気持ちに
悪口なんか 言ったりして｡
そんな お前が
わながあるのを 知ってて➡
If you want to go in there to fight despite it being a trap...
あえて 戦うというのなら➡
...then you must have found a way to beat Cars.
カーズを倒す作戦も
必ず あるのだろう｡
I've changed my mind!
気が変わったぜ！
If you're going in, then I'm right behind you...
昼間 決戦を挑むというなら
俺も 一緒に乗り込むぜ！
シーザー･ツェペリ！
...Caesar Zeppeli!
One set of footprints went inside.
昨夜 降った雪に 足跡が１つ…｡
なっ!?
こ… こいつは!?
W-Who was that?
今 何か 見えたようだったが
目の錯覚か？
I swear I saw someone!
Am I seeing things?
No, that's not an illusion!
いや違う 錯覚じゃあねえ！
何だ？ こいつは!?
What the hell is that?!
Caesar?
(人影)シーザーか…｡
くうっ！
あっ！ また消えた！
He vanished!
But I know he's here somewhere!
見えたり消えたり…
しかし いる！
５ｍ以内の どこかにいる！
He can only be a few steps away!
Does Cars have a new technique?
カーズの新しい術か？
No, the sun is too strong.
いや 太陽が
こんなに 照りつけているのに➡
He can't be outside!
やつが 外に出られるわけはない！
The Cat Stance, an element of kenpo.
〈猫足立ち！
中国拳法の構えである｡➡
もちろん シーザーは
拳法を習ったわけではないが➡
Caesar has never once heard of kenpo.
He relaxed his limbs,
ready to attack without losing his speed or rhythm!
四肢の力を抜き
どこの方向からの 攻撃にも➡
スピードと リズムを失わぬ
防御態勢を➡
He did all of this reflexively.
本能的に 取ったのである〉
Caesar!
≪(ﾒｯｼｰﾅ)シーザー！
あっ！
What are you doing? Going to this hotel alone is madness!
(ﾒｯｼｰﾅ)何をしている!?
１人で ホテルへ入るなど無謀！
Stay back, instructor!
近づくな 師範代！
(ﾒｯｼｰﾅ)んっ!?
俺は 今
中へ入るどころか 一歩も動けん｡
I can't move, let alone go inside.
Something is hiding in the entrance!
扉 入り口を中心に
何かが 潜んでいる！
What's that?
(ﾒｯｼｰﾅ)何だと!?
わしには 何も見え…｡
I can't see a-
It's a footprint!
あ… 足跡が１つだけ！
跳躍したんだ！
空中から 攻撃してくるぞ！
He jumped!
He's coming from above!
き… 貴様は!?
I-It's...
...Wham!
ワムウ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)むん！
(ﾒｯｼｰﾅ)ぐわ～！
メッシーナ師範代！
Instructor Messina!
ううっ！
くっ… なんてことだ｡
今のは ワムウだ｡
What the hell? That was Wham!
ワムウとカーズが
そろって この中にいるのか!?
Are he and Cars here together?
But how is Wham able to be outside during the day?
だが なぜだ？
ワムウが
太陽の下に出てくるなんて…｡
透明に見えるのと
関係があるのか？
He almost looks like a ghost.
うっ！
Where is that smart-mouthed trickster?
あの 減らず口をたたく
トッポイ男は どこだ？➡
Jojo...
ジョジョ
そう 成長したらしいな｡➡
I hear he's learned much.
エシディシ様を倒したやつは
どこにいる？
Where is the man who killed Master AC/DC?
Wind... I see, Wham can control the wind.
《風…
そうだ ワムウの流法は風！➡
The wind is making him transparent.
あの透明の正体は 風か？➡
やつの胸の辺りから 管が！➡
Air is coming from those pipes in his chest.
空気が出ている｡
わずかでも 目に見えるのは➡
It's only slightly visible because of water vapor.
水分を含んでいるからか…》
《そうか！➡
I've got it!
He's cloaking himself in vapor from those pipes!
ワムウは 自分の体の周りに➡
肺からの 水蒸気の渦を
まとわせているんだ！》
《恐らく それは 光の屈折現象》
It's refracting the light off him.
《その水蒸気が スーツとなって
太陽光線を屈折させ➡
It's like a suit that bends light, protecting him from the sun!
体を 光から守っているんだ｡➡
That's why he's transparent!
だから 透明のように見える！》
ジョジョは いないらしいな…｡
I see Jojo isn't here.
貴様は シャボン玉を使う
シーザーとかいったな｡
You're the bubble-user Caesar, correct?
今の身のこなしから 判断すると
相当に 修行を積み➡
Just by looking at you, I can see you've also learned much.
成長したと見える…｡
ううっ…｡
Very well. You are worthy of death
at the hands of the mighty Wham!
(ﾜﾑｳ)いいだろう！
まず この ワムウに
殺される資格はある！
ぬうう！ なめんじゃあねえ！
We'll just see who dies!
Right now, I feel the same way I did back in those slums!
俺の精神テンションは 今
貧民街時代に戻っている！
Just like when you killed my father!
父が 貴様らの わなに殺された
あの当時にだ！
I'll use my rage to destroy you!
冷酷！ 残忍！
その俺が 貴様を倒すぜ！
ぐっ！ 貴様の風は
俺のシャボンを 吹き飛ばす➡
Don't think your wind will just blow my bubbles away!
だなんて 安心するなよ！
風を突っ切る シャボンもある！
I've got bubbles that can even slice through wind!
I updated my grandfather Zeppeli's Ripple Cutter!
じいさんツェペリが 使ったという
波紋カッターの応用編！
シャボンカッター！
Bubble Cutter!
High speed rotation turns the bubble cutters into disks!
高速回転を加え 円盤状に変形した
シャボンカッター！
My Ripple ensures they won't pop!
波紋を帯びてるから
割れることなし！
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぬん!?
ワムウ！
Wham, the wind protecting you is just air to them!
貴様の 風のプロテクターは
まるで 換気扇よ！
身を守るどころか 逆に➡
Instead of defending you, it will draw the bubbles in!
俺のシャボンを
吸い込んでいくぜ！
SHHHYYYYYYAAAAHH！➡
His skill with the Ripple is far greater than I expected.
(ﾜﾑｳ)こ… こいつの波紋の強さは
予想以上に 成長しておる！
フッ！
この波紋使いめ！
Damn Ripple Warrior!
Hold it! I won't let you enter the hotel!
おお～っと！
ホテルの中へ 逃しはせん！
Bubble Cutter: Gliding!
シャボンカッターグライディン！
ううっ！
足を捉え➡
Now, while you're off balance...
体勢が崩れたところを すかさず➡
...I'll give you a Ripple kick!
波紋蹴りで 攻撃してやる！
〈次の瞬間
シーザーは仰天した！➡
But Caesar was in for a shock!
Normally, if your legs give out, you try not to fall.
普通 足をすくわれたら
転ぶまいとする｡➡
日光から
ホテル内に 逃れようとすれば➡
Especially if you need to escape into the hotel from the sunlight.
なおさら 転べない！➡
しかし ワムウは！〉
However, Wham...
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぬん！
...fell backwards on purpose!
〈逆に
思いっ切り のけぞった！〉
ぐあっ！
He's not just an immortal monster!
《や… やつは
ただの 不死身の怪物ではない｡➡
With senses like that, he's a genius fighter as well!
この戦いに対する 勘のさえ！
怪物にして 戦闘の天才だ！》
《だが シャボンカッターで➡
But my Bubble Cutter must have done some damage.
かなりの 波紋ダメージを
受けたはず》
今こそ好機 勝算あり！
The advantage is mine!
俺には ホテル内で勝利する
作戦がある！
I have a way to beat you inside the hotel!
♬～
My nerves are honed to a razor edge.
《俺の全神経は 今
研ぎ澄まされている｡➡
I can even feel subtle changes in the air.
肌で 微妙な空気の動きまでも
分かるほどに！➡
I have the same intense feeling I had when I was in the slums.
貧民街時代の
ビリビリした感覚だ！➡
My breathing is normal. I'm not sweating.
それに 呼吸のリズムは正常
汗もかかねえ｡➡
最高の波紋を 練れるぜ！》
Perfect Ripple conditions!
あっ…｡
はっ！ メッシーナ師範代！
Instructor Messina!
うう…｡
≪(物音)
あっ…｡
Taken off your coat, have you, Wham?
風のプロテクターを解いて
姿を現したな ワムウ！
They're gone, both Caesar and Messina!
いない！
メッシーナも シーザーも｡
Are they already inside the hotel?
既に ホテル内に
入ってしまったのか!?
ん？
T-That's...
こ… これは!? 一体 何が!?
What happened?
食らえ ワムウ！
シャボンランチャー！
Take this, Wham!
Bubble Launcher!
ぬうんっ！
効かぬと言ったろう！
I said that won't work!
ふん！ はっ！
ぬんっ！
はっ！
Bubble Cutter!
シャボンカッター！
うう… くっ…｡
逃がすか！
Running?!
I refuse to run or hide!
逃げも隠れもせん！
ぐわっ！
おお…｡
コォー…｡
ふん！
ぬおおおおおおっ！
Bubble Cutter!
シャボンカッター！
ふんっ！ ぬんっ！
むう！
ううっ！
食らえ ワムウ！
Take this, Wham!
Bubble Cutter: Gliding!
シャボンカッターグライディン！
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぐっ…｡➡
ぐうう…｡➡
ぐあっ…｡
(ﾜﾑｳ)ぐうっ…｡
ワムウ！
Wham!
No more games!
もう有無を言わせぬ！ 秘技！
It's over!
(ﾜﾑｳ)神妙…｡
おっと待ちな！ 周りをよく見ろ！
Holy Sand-
Stop and look around you!
ヌ！
My Bubble Cutters are now Bubble Lenses floating in the air!
今までの シャボンカッターは➡
既に シャボンレンズとなって
滞空していたぜ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)レンズ!?
Lenses?
And that hole you knocked in the wall
is like the open shutter of a camera!
そして
貴様が ぶち砕いた壁の穴は➡
いわば カメラの 開きっ放しの
シャッターのようなもの！
The lenses send sunlight...
レンズが 外の日光を！
...right into the hotel!
ホテル内へ！
What?!
(ﾜﾑｳ)何!?
SYYYYAAAAHHHH！
You can't move!
もう動けまい！
貴様は フィルムだ！
You're film! A frozen film!
写真のフィルムだ！
You're completely exposed, Wham!
真っ黒に感光しろ ワムウ！
GUU… MOO…｡
Trying your barrier again?
再び 風のプロテクターを!?
I won't let you!
そうはさせん！
I'll finish you off with a direct Ripple blast!
今度こそ 直接
波紋を流し込んで とどめだ！
One point...
〈一点！ そして一瞬！
ほんの 一点の死角だった｡➡
...at one moment.
A tiny miscalculation.
レンズの光に シーザーの体が
影となった 一点｡➡
Caesar's body created a shadow at a single point!
Wham immediately took advantage of this mistake!
ワムウは
この一瞬を 逃さなかった！〉
はっ！
He showed Caesar once again that he was a fighting genius!
〈シーザーは ワムウが
戦闘の天才だということを➡
再び 思い知らされた！〉
Wind Mode! Holy Sandstorm!
(ﾜﾑｳ)風の流法 神砂嵐！
うわあっ！
ううっ…｡
ああっ！
こ… この破壊力は!?
S-Such destruction!
ま… まさか!?
I-It couldn't be!
It's Wham's Holy Sandstorm!
ワムウの神砂嵐！ それしかない！
So that means Caesar is-!
ということは シーザーが!?
(ﾜﾑｳ)フフフ…
なんと 強力に成長したものよ…｡
You've grown so much.
満足だ…
久しく 満足なる戦いだった｡
I am satisfied.
I haven't had such a fight in ages...
波紋の戦士よ｡
...warrior of the Ripple.
And it was such a close fight...
そして 危なかった…｡
もし 俺の流法が
お前の波紋レンズを➡
If my wind hadn't the strength to blow away your lenses...
吹き飛ばせる
風でなかったなら…➡
貴様のレンズからの 日光を➡
...I have no idea how I could have stopped the light.
どうやって防いでいたか
分からぬ｡
And if Master Cars, who cannot use wind, had met you here first...
(ﾜﾑｳ)そして もし
風の流法を利用しない➡
カーズ様が 先に
ここで お前と出会い➡
...and met your power...
戦っていたのなら…｡
ぐああっ！
負けるはずはないにせよ➡
Even if he had won...
...he would be in much worse shape than I am now.
私以上の苦戦と ダメージを
強いられていたであろう｡➡
ヌッ！
はぁ… はぁ…｡
Don't.
無駄だ｡ 貴様は もはや➡
You will not fight again.
立ち上がれるような
肉体ではない｡➡
My Holy Sandstorm has shredded your body.
流法 神砂嵐は お前の筋肉や
血管を ズタズタにしてしまった｡
はぁっ！
Stop. The battle is done.
(ﾜﾑｳ)やめろ 勝負はついた！
ううっ…｡
You have no more Ripple.
もはや
微量の波紋さえ 練れておらぬ｡
See?
見ろ それほどの多量の出血｡
You've almost bled out.
Understand that this means you have no hope.
(ﾜﾑｳ)
つまり もう お前は助からない｡
う… うああ…｡
ああ…｡
やめろ｡
Stop.
ううっ…｡
Goodbye.
さらばだ｡
お前の命は 今 終わった｡
Your life has ended.
はっ！ 何!?
What?!
フッ…｡
My piercing with the antidote. Why?
解毒剤入りのピアスを!?
なぜ 貴様が？
I-I'm... not afraid to die.
し… 死ぬのは怖くねえぜ…｡
だが 俺は…
誇り高きツェペリ家の男だ｡
But I am a proud member of the Zeppeli family...
It's in my blood...
その血統を 受け継いでいる｡
Something like this might mean nothing
to an inhuman monster like you...
こんなこと 人間でねえ
貴様なんかにしゃべっても➡
分からねえだろうがな…｡
My father didn't recognize me, but he sacrificed his life to save mine.
《父さんは この俺を
息子と知らなくても➡
自分の命を犠牲にして
救ってくれた》
My grandfather gave his Ripple energy
to Jojo's grandfather, Jonathan, before he died.
《じいさんも ジョジョの祖父
ジョナサンのために➡
波紋の力を与えて
死んでいったというぜ》
It's tradition. I have to do something.
《だから 俺だって
何か しなくっちゃあな》
I can't let my life's flame sputter out...
《カッコ悪くて
あの世に行けねえぜ》
俺が 最期に見せるのは➡
This is the Zeppeli family spirit, from the past to the future!
代々 受け継いだ
未来に託す ツェペリ魂だ！
人間の魂だ！
It's the human spirit!
ジョジョ！
俺の最期の波紋だぜ！
Jojo, this is the last of my Ripple!
Take it!
受け取ってくれ～‼
≪受け取ってくれ～‼
あっ！
That's Caesar's voice!
シーザーの声だ！
聞こえたか？ シーザーだ！
Did you hear him?
Yes.
聞こえたわ！
まさか シーザーが!?
But Caesar can't be-!
Caesar!
シーザー‼
♬～
(ﾜﾑｳ)やつの血で作った
シャボン玉か…｡➡
He made a bubble from his blood...
It must have taken all of his Ripple to make it.
割れないところを見ると
最後の波紋を 絞り切ったようだ｡
He saved it for this moment,
for his friends, rather than using it on me.
仲間のため これを残すため➡
さっきは 波紋を込めず
俺を殴ったのか｡
Let them have it.
くれてやる｡➡
人間のように
センチになったからではない｡
It's not because I'm sentimental like humans.
俺にとって
強い戦士こそ 真理｡
His talent as a fighter was profound.
He has my respect as a fellow warrior.
勇者こそ 友であり 尊敬する者｡➡
I will hold you forever in my memory, Caesar.
俺は お前のことを 永遠に➡
記憶の片隅に
とどめておくであろう｡➡
シーザー…｡
(ﾜﾑｳ)シャボン玉のように
華麗で はかなき男よ｡
A man as splendid and as fleeting as his bubbles.
♬～
T-This place is in ruins!
こ… この破壊状態は…｡
Wham's Holy Sandstorm must have done this!
確かに ワムウの神砂嵐！
これを 食らったのが
シーザーだったなら！
And Caesar was caught in it.
あっ！
A bubble...
シャボン玉が…｡
C-Could it be...
こ… これは!? まさか!?
It can't!
It's Caesar's bandana!
これは シーザーのバンダナ！
そして ピアス！
And...
A piercing! Wham's lip piercing!
ワムウのピアスだ！
うっ…｡
ああっ！
The feeling of this Ripple energy...
この波紋エネルギーの 感覚は!?
It... It can't be!
そ… そんな!?
う… うう…｡
I haven't called Caesar's name since we got here.
俺は このホテルに入ってから➡
一度も
シーザーの名を呼んでねえ｡
なぜって 呼ぶのが怖かった｡
It was because I was afraid.
If I cried out his name and there was no response...
もし シーザーって
大声で 呼んだのに➡
返事が 返って
こなかったなら｡
し～んとした静寂
だけだったらって➡
If the only response was silence... That's what scared me.
それが恐ろしかった｡
I couldn't accept it.
認めたくなかった｡
So I didn't call him...
だから
呼ばなかった｡
But now I know.
でも 今 分かった｡
The Ripple in that bubble told me everything.
今のシャボンの
波紋の感覚で➡
全てが分かった｡
シーザーは 今
さっき ここで死んだ！
Caesar, just moments ago...
...died right here.
Caesar, you bastard. You were a showoff 'till the end.
シーザーの野郎…｡
まったく 最後の最後まで➡
キザな野郎だぜ｡
Leaving a gift like this...
こんな 置き土産まで
していくなんてよ｡
Caesar, where are you?!
シーザー！
お前 どこだ!?
Where are you sleeping?!
どこに 眠っている!?
今 捜してやる！
I'll find you! I'll dig you up! Caesar!
掘り起こしてやる！ シーザー！
Jojo!
ジョジョ！
うっ…｡
シーザーを悲しむのも
捜すことも許しません｡
We don't have time to waste searching or grieving for Caesar.
What?!
何!?
There are two of them and two of us. Two versus two.
これで 向こうも２人｡
我々も２人｡ ２対２｡
And the only thing we know by that blood trail
is that Caesar badly injured Wham.
しかし あの
転々と続く 血を見ると➡
ワムウは シーザーから
かなり ダメージを➡
受けたようです｡
既に 敵地に
入ったからには➡
We're in enemy territory.
Let's go and finish it!
このまま
決戦を挑むまで！
ぐっ…｡
ジョジョ いいですね？
Jojo, come on.
その解毒剤を飲んだら
奥へ やつを追います！
Take the antidote, then we'll hunt them.
《こ… この女！➡
T-This woman...
シーザーのために
涙一つ 流さねえのか!?》
Not even a single tear for Caesar?!
うっ… くっ…｡
リサリサ先生 たばこ 逆さだぜ｡
Master Lisa Lisa...
...your cigarette's backwards.
《リサリサは 先生だ｡➡
Lisa Lisa is our master, she has to keep a calm demeanor.
わざと
冷酷さを装っている》
I know she wants to cry much more than I do...
《今 一番
泣き叫びたいのは➡
彼女の方だ｡➡
He treated her like a goddess, and knew her much longer than I did.
女神のごとく
慕われていたし➡
つきあいも
俺以上に 長いんだからな》
I have to hold my feelings back.
《俺にも
感情を 抑えろってことか…》
Caesar, I know you thought I was self-centered...
《シーザー お前が評する
自分勝手な このジョジョが➡
But just now, I understood how someone else was feeling.
今 相手の気持ちを読んで
こともあろうか 思いやったぜ｡➡
少しは 成長したかな…》
I guess I'm a little more mature.
だがな やつらに対しては
とことん 鬼になってやるぜ！
However, I'll show no sympathy when I fight these beasts!
I've inherited your fighting spirit!
お前の心！ 確かに受け取った！
(板が崩れる音)
うっ!?
ああ…｡
ち… 血が｡
It... It's blood...
シーザーが そこに…｡
Caesar... right here...
あ…｡
シーザー…｡
Caesar...
ああ…｡
シーザー… うっ…｡
Caesar...
ああ…｡
Caesar!
シーザー‼
うああ～‼
This is enemy territory. Cars and Wham are nearby.
〈ここは 敵地｡➡
どこかに
ワムウとカーズが 潜んでいる｡➡
しかし ２人は
感情を抑え切れなかった〉
But neither of them could hold it in.
〈ジョジョは叫んだ
シーザーの名を｡➡
Jojo cried out Caesar's name.
Lisa Lisa shed tears of pain and sorrow.
リサリサは流した
悲しみの涙を｡➡
But their cries were only answered by cold silence.
けれども シーザーの名を呼んでも
返ってくるのは 残酷な静寂だけ〉
Caesar was gone.
〈シーザーは 死んだのだ〉
For Jojo and Lisa Lisa, the silence only confirmed the truth.
〈ジョジョと リサリサは➡
静寂によって
この事実を 実感した〉
〈その身 尽きても
その魂は 死なず｡➡
Though his body had died, his soul lived on.
Rest in peace, Caesar Zeppeli.
シーザー･ツェペリ ここに眠る〉
In and around the lake
Mountains come out of the sky
They stand there
Twenty four before my love and I'll be there
私は 今 機嫌が悪い｡
(ﾍﾞｯｸ)抱き締めの お仕置きズラ！
(ﾜﾑｳ)今夜は満月！ 時はそれ！
(ｶｰｽﾞ)貴様らに 明日はない！
一緒に戦ってくれ シーザー！
Next Episode
I'm in a bad mood.
I'll hug you to death!
We fight tonight, under the full moon.
You have no tomorrow!
Fight alongside me, Caesar!
Episode 21:
"One-Hundred Versus Two"